The worst day of my life.
Let's go party.
I'm on my way to Seoul to throw my
friend a surprise bachelorette party. I
didn't buy my train ticket far enough in
advance, so I have to stand. Lesson
learned. Next time, I'll be more on top
of things.
I made it to Seoul, and the first thing
on my agenda is to pick up a cake that I
ordered for Illeque, the bride-to-be. My
friend Lorena, who's in on the surprise,
is going to meet me at the bakery. She's
going to give me a hand because I've
still got my suitcase with me.
Cake secured. Lorena to the rescue.
>> Do you want me to carry this?
>> Thanks.
>> I got a little bit like pulled
yesterday.
>> Cake reveal. Instead of life of the
party, it says wife of the party since
she's getting married. So cute. We're on
our way to a grocery store to buy some
snacks, and then we're heading to a
liquor store to get some champagne.
We're going to pop some bottles tonight.
We bought some decorations for the
house, so I'm blowing up some balloons.
>> Is Mango going to pop them?
>> She'll pop one and then be scared of
one.
Loe is hanging the balloons and
streamers. Teamwork.
Ellie is on her way and we are still
trying to clean up the house and get
everything ready. So, I'm trying to buy
us time. I asked her to go to the
convenience store to buy me some snacks
because I'm hungry. She even video
chatted me to show me which snacks are
available. I'm trying to be picky just
to take up some more time. Sorry, Ellie.
>> A few moments later.
>> My heart is racing. I'm nervous.
I come with the snacks and everything.
No way.
I I I thought I was going to miss this
year.
>> It's your mini bachelorette party.
>> This is happy tears.
>> Oh, good. That's why I was being so
annoying. I was buying time. Did you
expect anything?
>> I thought maybe you'll buy a cake, but I
was like, I hope they don't because my
birthday has been like a month ago.
>> Mhm. But, did you think we were going to
do like a bride thing?
Now you
Dear Ellie, in the name of love we crown
you bride-to-be.
>> I want to say thank you, my people.
>> I'm putting on her sash. Okay, queen.
Let's go party.
>> We have to put the veil, too.
>> Oh, yeah.
So pretty.
Ooh, she's a bride.
The bride's out in the wild.
Get us some free drinks, girl, or some
free sushi.
>> it.
>> Don't be shy. Work it, girl. Work it.
>> Work it.
>> I love it.
>> Oh, who is that? It's mystery woman
behind the veil.
>> Ta-da!
This place did not disappoint.
>> Miss you, T.
>> It's because of the sash and the crown.
Being silly.
>> It's very nice. It's very nice.
The drink The drink is very nice.
>> We just had sushi for dinner, and now
we're going to take photos in a photo
booth.
>> This is like a passport photo.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly, you kind of blinked.
>> I know.
>> Let's just do it this for fun.
>> Okay.
>> What time is it?
>> Karaoke time.
>> It's the remix to Ignition. Choose a
Choose a song.
Mango, what did you do?
>> You see the mango?
>> It's so funny. We put on our PJs, popped
some popcorn, and we're about to watch a
chick flick. What are we watching?
>> The Family Stone.
>> The Family Stone. It's a tearjerker, but
it's so good. You guys are going to love
it.
>> We're ready to cry.
>> Yeah.
>> We're ready.
>> Get your tissues ready.
>> Mask break time.
>> Good morning. We stayed up until 2:00 in
the morning yesterday. I'm not a night
owl at all, so I'm a little bit sleepy,
but Mango was my sleeping buddy. We
cuddled all night, and it was so cute.
Now, we're about to head to brunch and
get some food in our tummies.
So, Ellie, how was the bachelorette
party?
>> The bachelorette party was awful, the
worst day of my life.
>> Savage.
It's going to be our hook.
Can you tell me a little bit about your
wedding coming up?
>> Yes. I am so excited about our wedding.
It's been in the making for a lot of
years now, because we were planning to
get married back in 2020. However, COVID
hit. We had to cancel our wedding plans.
So, now, finally, the timing is right
again, and we are going to do it in
Bulgaria. We are planning to do an
outdoor wedding, so I'm excited about
that. I really hope it's going to be
great sunny This is the only thing I'm
very worried about. Knock on wood.
>> Do you have any honeymoon plans?
>> Yes, we do. We are planning to go on a
kind of a long trip. Our first
destination is going to be Egypt, and we
are actually going there with my
parents, because I wanted to make them a
small gift as well.
>> They're crashing your honeymoon?
>> Yes,
but I love my parents, so it's going to
be great. And then, the rest of the
honeymoon trip is going to be a
surprise, because we're planning to vlog
it as well.
>> I'll link her channel, so you can check
her out.
>> Yay! Bye!
Love you!
>> I made it back to Busan, and I already
miss my friends. We all live in
different cities, so it's pretty rare
for all three of us to get together.
Usually, at bachelorette parties, you
drink a lot and party hard, but we
stayed sober, kept it pretty low-key,
and still had a blast. For my
bachelorette party, I went bar-hopping
in Itaewon with a group of friends, and
it got pretty wild. Planning a wedding
is usually really stressful, so I think
a bachelorette party is a great way to
just let loose and forget about that
stress for one night. Anyways, it's time
to catch up on sleep. Good night.